Guide to the Stanford University Architectural Collection SC1043
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- McMurtry Building for Art & Art History drawings, 1996-2015; Accession ARCH-2016-115
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University 50% Construction Documents, 2012-12-03 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University 50% Construction Documents, 2012-12-03 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University Bid Set - Revision 1 Volume 1, 2013-04-15 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University Bid Set - Revision 1 Volume 2, 2013-04-15 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Additional Drawings, Accession ARCH-2017-185
  - Various drawings, mostly Chemistry Labs (Box 1-3)
- Additional Drawings, Accession ARCH-2017-271
  - Foung Weisbard House Remodel Floor Plan, 1992 Apr 15; A_1; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Architect: Christopher Tripoll
  - Foung Weisbard House Remodel Existing Floor Plan Demolition Plan, 1992 Apr 15; A_2; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 1)
  - Foung Weisbard House Remodel 668 Mayfield Site Plan, 1992 May 04; A_3; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 1)
  - Foung Weisbard House Remodel North and West Elevation, 1992 Apr 15; A_4; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 1)
  - Foung Weisbard House Remodel South and East Elevation, 1992 Apr 15; A_5; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 1)
  - Foung Weisbard House Remodel Interiors, 1992 Apr 15; A_6; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 1)
  - Foung Weisbard House Remodel Footing, 1992 Apr 15; A_7; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 1)
  - Foung Weisbard House Remodel Kitchen Remodel, 1997 Jan 13; A_1; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 1)
  - Foung Weisbard House Remodel Kitchen Remodel, 1996 May 28; A_2; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 1)
  - 666 Mayfield House Floor Area, 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 2)
    Architect: J.K. Branner
  - 666 Mayfield House Floor Area, 1; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 2)
  - 666 Mayfield House Front Elevation, 3; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 2)
  - 666 Mayfield House End Elevation, 5; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 2)
  - 666 Mayfield House Roof View, 6; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 2)
  - 666 Mayfield House Before Plan, 2; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 2)
  - 666 Mayfield House Rear Elevation, 4; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 2)
  - Building 32 Rear Elevation, 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 3)
    Architect: Wolfe & Higgins
  - Building 32 Rear Elevation, 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 3)
  - Building 32 Front Elevation, 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 3)
  - Prof. J.L. Mothershead Plan of Workroom, 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 4)
    Architect: J.N. Cabbage
  - Mothershead 666 Mayfield Avenue Floor Plan and Front Elevation, 21_A; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 4)
  - Gunite Swimming Pool, 1957 Nov 19; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 4)
    Architect: Dolphin Pools
  - 16 X 38 Pool for Mothershead, 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 4)
  - Pool Typical Wall Sections, 1956 Jun 01; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 4)
  - Swimming Pool Plan, 1957 Sep 05; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 4)
    Architect: Church and Associates
  - Revised Lot for Mothershead, 1957 Jan 11; 154; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 5)
  - Specifications for Mothershead Playroom, 1941 Oct 11; S_3; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 5)
    Architect: Morgan Stedman
  - Specifications for Prof Mrs Mothershead, S_2; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 5)
  - Present Plan Proposed Alterations to Mothershead Residence, 1941 Oct 04; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 5)
  - Mothershead Proposed Addition, 1941 Oct 07; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 5)
  - Alterations to Residence of Prof Mrs. Mothershead - Laundry and Servants Room, 1941 Aug 11; 1; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 5)
  - Proposed Additions to Residence of Prof. Mrs. Mothershead - Playroom Dets., 2; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 5)
  - Proposed Additions to Residence of Prof. Mrs. Mothershead - Sect. A, B, C, 3; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 5)
  - Specifications for Prof. Mrs. Mothershead, 1947 Sep 22; S_1; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 5)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace Plot Plan and services, 1939 Aug 17; 752_M1b; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
    Architect: Hunter & Hudson
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace Duct Shaft Details Main Steam Riser Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans, 1939 Nov 10; 752_M8; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace Basement Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09; 752_E1; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace First Foor Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09; 752_E2; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace Second Floor Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 10; 752_E3; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace Third Floor Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09; 752_E4; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace 5th, 9th, 10th 11th Floors Electrical Equipment Plans (1 of 2), 1939 Oct 09; 752_E5; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace 5th, 9th, 10th 11th Floors Electrical Equipment Plans (1 of 2), 1939 Oct 09; 752_E5; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace 12-16th floors Electrical Equipment Plans (1 of 2), 1939 Oct 09; 752_E6; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace 12-16th floors Electrical Equipment Plans (2 of 2), 1939 Oct 09; 752_E6; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace Stairway Elevations Diagrams, 1939 Oct 09; 752_E7; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace Basement Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09; 752_E1; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace First Floor Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09; 752_E2; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace Second Floor Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09; 752_E3; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace Third Floor Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09; 752_E4; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace 5th, 9th, 10th 11th Floors Electrical Equipment Plans (1 of 2), 1939 Oct 09; 752_E5; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace 5th, 9th, 10th 11th Floors Electrical Equipment Plans (1 of 2), 1939 Oct 09; 752_E5; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace 12-16th floors Electrical Equipment Plans (1 of 2), 1939 Oct 09; 752_E6; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Revolution and Peace Stairway Elevations Diagrams, 1939 Oct 09; 752_E7; 1 architectural drawing(s) (Box 6)